- Margaret.
What the hell am I
supposed to do with this?
- Doctor's orders, honey.
No saturated fat.
- Ma'am, that doctor is a hack.
And he's pathetic.
He shouldn't even
have a license.
Stop listening to the doctor.
Jesus.
You give me bread?
First of all it's not toasted,
second of all it's peanut
butter without any jam.
How do you expect me to
swallow this or get it down?
How many goddamn times do
I have to tell you that?
Get your nose out of a
cookbook and learn to make
a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
- Keep talking like that
and you'll be making
your own sandwiches.
- What did you say?
What was that?
- According to the Global
Health Education Consortium,
there are numerous social
causes for violence.
Poverty, unemployment,
illicit drug and alcohol
abuse, cultural norms.
But these external influences
don't explain the root
cause of violence.
Texas versus Johnson.
Ed Johnson was charged
with first degree murder
after the deaths of
his ex-girlfriend
and a boy she was seeing.
Because of the
heinousness of the crimes,
and the ages of the victims,